# **Adam Mayer**

Perth, Western Australia +-| Phone: 0466 556 976 | Email: amayer.dataanalyse@gmail.com

LinkedIn: /adam-mayer-diamond | GitHub: /ACMayer

#### **SUMMARY**

A hardworking, analytical and energised Data Professional whose background is in Exercise and Sports Science. I have officiated sports for 9 years and coached/mentored for 7 years, showing commitment and self-development.

I have a strong passion to enhance my newly learned data analytics skills in a team environment and am actively seeking a position which will allow me to continue my professional development within an organization.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

**Languages**: Python, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, SQL, NoSQL, Visual Basic for Applications, Pandas **Applications**: GitHub, Excel, APIs, Git Bash, Tableau, Visual Studio Code, Jupyter Notebook

Data: PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Leaflet, TensorFlow, D3.js, BeautifulSoup, SQLAlchemy, Flask Other: High Level of Attention to Detail, Mentoring, Creative Problem Solving, Leadership and an

Innovative Approach.

### **PROJECTS**

We, The New York Squirrels | https://github.com/alyssahondrade/we-the-new-york-city-squirrels

This project focused on the 2018 and 2020 Squirrel Censuses respectively, and creates an interactive dashboard depicting a squirrel's day-to-day life in New York City

Role: Analyst and contributor

 Languages (and Libraries): Python (Pandas, Flask), SQL Alchemy, JavaScript (Leaflet, D3.js), HTML/CSS

Tools: Git Bash, Jupyter Notebook

Crowdfunding | https://github.com/ed2131/Crowdfunding\_ETL

This project will demonstrate how data files have been cleaned using Python and then queried using SQL. Initially there was exploration done in the pandas data frames, then the data was cleaned and saved. After which SQL code creates a database schema and performs queries on the data.

Role: Analyst and contributor

- Languages (and Libraries): Python (Pandas), SQL
- Tools: Git Bash, Jupyter Notebook

Project 4 | https://github.com/aaronbilbow/Project4|

This project focused on classifying medical images through a machine learning model into one of the 6 different categories provided by the MNIST dataset on Kaggle. This model was designed with the intention to assist with future models that may have a healthy database reference point and then slowly build in parts of the model to identify diseases.

- Role: Analyst and contributor
- Languages (and Libraries): Python (pandas, pathlib, numpy, matplotlib) SKlearn, Keras, Tensorflow, Pillow
- Tools: Git Bash, Jupyter Notebook, Power Point, Streamlit

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

# Football Coach/ Mentor UWA, Stirling Macedonia, Subiaco AFC

2017- Present

- Detailed planning, organisation and delivery of training sessions tailored to both junior development and match performance.
- Video analysis for my own knowledge but also presenting data to players and other coaches.
- Mentoring adult and youth players.
- Communicating with stakeholders, delivered by various means in a clear concise and timely manner.
- Organising referees and pitches to ensure adequate space available for friendly matches to be held.

### **Onsite Medical Care - (Short term Casual Contract)**

02/2021 - 06/2021

#### Administration Support

- Providing administration support while the company prepared for accreditation under Australian Health Standards Association
- Daily administration duties to assist the clinical and management teams, including answering phone calls, corresponding with specialists and other external providers, scanning and filing.
- Database entry including medical records, ensuring patient confidentiality was always maintained.
- Creating patient files and patient information packs, including health information, feedback forms and surveys

## State Basketball League Referee

01/2015 -10/2018

- Analysing game footage for the development of myself and others
- Communicating with players, coaches and score bench
- · Creating a personal development plan for myself
- Diffusing potentially difficult situations engaging various techniques

# Perry Lakes, Warwick, Joondalup Basketball Referee, Referee Coach/ Mentor

2013 - 2020

- Creating the development plan for junior referees and mentoring them through this process
- Collaboratively designing assessment criteria for referees
- Organising and scheduling referees for both regular season and finals fixtures
- Mentoring of players and coaches in application and interpretation of rules
- Communicating effectively with players, coaches, score bench officials and spectators

### **EDUCATION**

Data Analytics Certificate, University of Western Australia Bachelor of Science (Exercise &Sports Science), Edith Cowan Perth, 07/2023-01/2024 Perth, 2014/2018

#### OTHER PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

#### **Football Federation Australia Certificates**

FFA B Licence Coaching
FFA C Licence Coaching
Perth,2020/21
Perth,2018

#### **Basketball Western Australia Certificates**

Level 1 Basketball Referee
Level 1 Basketball Referee Coach
Perth,2014
Perth,2016